Hey friends, I'm Scott Hanselman.
Hey 大家好，我是 Scott Hanselman.
And I'm Maria Naggaga.
我是 Maria Naggaga
And this is Microsoft Virtual Academy.
这里是微软虚拟学院
We're gonna be talking about ASP.NET Core 2.
我们将会讨论有关 ASP.NET Core 2.0 的内容
>> Yes, we are.
是的
Right, we've got three days of great content for you
好的，我们将用三天的时间给你展现精彩的内容
This is the beginner day, we're gonna have beginner
这是第一天，我们会从初学者开始
getting started, a little bit about .NET and C#, and
开始前，你需要一点有关
the resources that you'll need.
.NET 和 C# 的资源
Maria and I will explore creating a web application.
Maria 与我将会探索创建一个 Web 应用
And by the end of these three days, you should be ready to go
当这三天结束后，你应当能够准备好
and make a web application for yourself.
为自己制作一个 Web 应用程序
Exactly, and a good place to get started here is for
准确的说，这是一个让你们知道在哪里
people to figure out where to get the tools they need
可以找到你们所需要工具的
to get started   Yeah, so if you go to
好地方！            是的，如果你进入
dot.net, we made a little fun domain for you here d-o-t.net.
"http://dot.net",我们为你们制作了一个有趣的域名
Or if you go out there and
或者 如果你离开这里
search with your favorite search engine for learn C# or
通过你最喜爱的搜索引擎去索引 "C#" 或者
download .NET you will probably end up showing up here.
"下载.NET"，你也会找到这个网址
The page might look something like this,
页面可能看起来可能与这个很相似
might be a little different by the time time has passed.
也许也会随着时间的推移有所改变吧
But you'll click on Download and
但是，你点击下载
you're gonna see three different .NETs to choose from.
你会看到不同的三个 .NET 选项
There is the .NET Framework, that comes with Windows.
这是 .NET Framework ，它运行在 Windows 上
There is Xamarin, which let's you make IOS, and Android, and
这是 Xamarin ，它能让你制作 iOS，Android，以及
Windows applications.
Windows 平台应用
We're gonna be focusing on .NET Core, aren't we?
但我们要把重心放在 .NET Core 上，是吧？
>> Yes, we are.
是呀！
So if you click on that it should show you a couple
所以，如果你点击这他的话，应该会给你展示几个
of options on how to get started.
关于如何开始的选项
And then a lot of things that come up, especially for
然后，很多内容出现了，值得注意的是
new people to our platform, is do they download the SDK or
对于我们平台的新人来说，选择下载 SDK 呢
the runtime?
还是 RunTime 呢？
Right, so the SDK, that's the tools, the compiler, the stuff I
是的，像 SDK ，其实是种工具和编译器，
need as a developer because it's the software development kit
是作为开发人员所必需的东西，它是软件开发的工具包
Yeah.
对的
So you probably will never want the runtime unless you're
所以，你可能永远不需要运行时 RunTime ，除非你
gonna put that into production.
要把它投入特定生产环境中
And then if you really want more information, you can follow step
然后，如果你真的想要更多的信息，你可以按照
by step instructions down here at the bottom.
下面的一步一步的说明去探索。
Yeah, and we should actually click on one of those.
是的，我们应该点击其中的一个
Click on the Windows one and you should see not only a step
点击一下 Windows ，你不仅可以看到一个清晰的步骤
by step, but also a few videos in between.
而且还能看到中间有说明的视频。
Right, so we've got a little video, this is very very short
是的，所以我们可以看到一些短视频，他们非常的短
two or three minutes, not as fun as this video, but still.
有两到三分钟，虽然不像这部视频这么有趣，但也差不多~
By you download the .NET SDK,
你下载了 .NET SDK 之后
it will pick the right version for you.
它将自动为您选择所需的版本
And then by the end of this little three or
然后通过这最后在这三个或
four step process, you will have written your first .NET app,
四个步骤，你就可以编写你的第一个 .NET 应用程序了
which I think we will do in a little bit.
我想我们会在这上面做一点的
All right, so you can also of course,
好的，其实你也可以
get your different versions of Linux, you can do it on a Mac,
获取不同的版本，你像 Linux ，你也可以在 Mac 上面运行它
and you can also use Docker, so there's a lot of options.
甚至还可以部署在 Docker 上，所以是有好多选择的！
.NET Core runs everywhere.
.NET Core 可以跑在任何地方（微软大法好）
Everywhere, and you can get this to run in ten minutes.
还有，你可以在十分钟内让它跑起来
Or less, really.
哇，真的太棒了
So the other thing that you might want to think about is our documentation.
还有，你可能会考虑有关我们的文档的事情
If you go to docs.microsoft.com and your country of choice.
如果你去 "docs.microsoft.com" 并且选好你所在的国家
This docs right here is got all the different docs through all
就可以看到这里有好多文档，所有的文档！
the different Microsoft properties.
有好多不同微软特性的技术
So Azure and Xamarian and bots and all kinds of fun stuff.
像 Azure Xamarian 还有 Bot Framework 各种各样的类型
When you go to .NET, there's a ton of great things and
当你进入到 .NET ，有很多很棒的事情
we're gonna go through this a little bit more and
我们会深入了解一下
show you some of the fun things inside.
并向你展示一些有趣的东西
But remember, we're focusing on .NET Core, C# and ASP.NET.
但是请记住，我们关注的是 .Net Core C# 和 ASP.NET
That's what we're doing.
这就是我们正在做的
All right, and
是的
the last thing that you wanna think about is Visual Studio.
还有最后一件事是 Visual Studio
And there are Visual Studio options.
还有 Visual Studio 选项
So you have Visual Studio IDE which is on Windows, right?
你在 Windows 上有 Visual Studio IDE 对吧？
And if you scroll across just a little bit,
只要稍稍移动一下屏幕
there's Visual Studio Code.
就可以看到 Visual Studio Code 了
And if you scroll just a little bit down on to the next level,
如果稍稍向下滚动一点
you'll see the different options.
你会看到另外的选择
You have Visual Studio for Mac now as well, and
你现在也可以获取 Visual Studio for Mac 了
you can build your ASP.NET Core application there.
你可以在 Mac 上创建 ASP.NET Core  应用
So anything that we're doing today,
所以，我们今天所做的任何事情
people can do this on their Mac.
人们都可以在他们的 Mac 上完成
Good point, so even though I'm on a Surface book,
这是很好的一点，所以即使我用的是运行着Windows的
I'm running Windows, literally every single thing that we're
Surface Book，但我想展示的是
gonna show you today, you should be able to follow along on your Mac
我们可以方便的的做到相同的事，不论是在你的 Mac 上
on your Ubuntu machine, on your Windows machine.
Ubuntu 设备上或者 Windows 设备上
I will be using Visual Studio code a little bit
我将更多的使用 Visual Studio Code
I'll be using Visual Studio a little bit, but you should be
因为 Visual Studio Code 太棒了，但是呢
able to follow along in your favorite editor, all right?
如果你愿意，你也可以用别的，好吧？
Yeah.
是的
Cool, we'll take a quick pause and we'll come back with the next module.
太棒啦，我们将快速休整一下，进入下一个模块